<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movies</string>

    <!--Fields for corresponding api keys-->
    <!--<string name="api_key"></string>-->
    <!--<string name="youtube_api_key"></string>-->

    <!--Strings for menu elements-->
    <string name="preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="preferences_title">Movies preferences</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>

    <!--Strings for preferences-->
    <string name="list_title">Show Movies by:</string>
    <string name="criteria_key">criteria</string>
    <string-array name="criteria_entries">
        <item>Now playing</item>
        <item>Most popular</item>
        <item>Top rated</item>
        <item>Upcoming</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="criteria_values">
        <item>now_playing</item>
        <item>popular</item>
        <item>top_rated</item>
        <item>upcoming</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="criteria_default">now_playing</string>

    <!--Strings for activity_main layout-->
    <string name="non_loading_message">There has been an error, please check your Internet connection and try again</string>

    <!--Strings for activity_detail layout-->
    <string name="trailer_button">Trailer\ </string>
    <string name="active_video">It seems trailer #%1$d is already being played</string>
    <string name="genres_descriptor">Genres:</string>
    <string name="budget_descriptor">Budget:</string>
    <string name="producers_descriptor">Producers:</string>
    <string name="vote_average_descriptor">Vote average:</string>
    <string name="release_date_descriptor">Release date:</string>
    <string name="description_descriptor">Description:</string>

    <!--Strings for reviews content-->
    <string name="movie_reviews_title">Movie Reviews</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">I just came back home from watching Aquaman on the IMAX theater in Balexert in Geneva and thought that I should write something up while it’s still fresh in my mind. Something that happens all too rarely.\r\n\r\nI have to say that, overall, I had quite a blast watching this movie. It is indeed a good superhero and special effects extravaganza. In addition it is quite beautiful. A lot of the underwater scenes are very pleasing on the eye indeed. I am quite happy that I managed to drag my ass over to a theater and watch it on a IMAX screen. Some of the hype around it is perhaps a bit too much though. It does not quite reach the masterpiece level after all.\r\n\r\nStorywise, well it is a superhero movie after all so if you expect the story to be profound, logical and watertight you should lay off those mushrooms or whatever you are smoking. That said, the story was not too bad. Pretty straightforward and not too convoluted. A good, solid story suitable for a action/adventure movie.\r\n\r\nI did quite like the main protagonists on the good side. Especially Jason Momoa as Aquaman. I mean his time-to-kick-some-ass-stare was just so…evil. The script writer had put some stupid shit in there where he had to play overly dumb at times but on the whole he was a good guy throughout the entire movie. Almost no whining, angst and anti-hero shit like what have totally ruined most of the Marvel TV-shows lately.\r\n\r\nThe bad guys were not too bad either. Orm was lacking a bit in the bad guy charisma department but Black Manta was oozing despicable bad bad bad asshole from the first scene to the last. I probably should not say this because his weird helmet is indeed true to the comics but, well, it’s weird and kind of looks better in a comics than on the big screen.\r\n\r\nSpecial effects? Well, there is not that much to say really. They are pretty awesome throughout the movie and, as I wrote above, a lot of the time they are also beautiful. The various creatures, underwater vehicles and gadgets are really cool and well designed.\r\n\r\nThe one gripe I have about the movie is the totally unnecessary green preaching crap. Luckily it is confined to a couple of scenes but in those it is really slapped in the audience’s faces. A superhero movie should be entertaining, not preaching. If I want that shit I can turn on the news. It’s a star off from me just for that nonsense."</string>
    <string name="dummy_author">James Unkown</string>
    <string name="review_author">Author</string>
</resources>
